If today's show was put on for me,
then my reaction
might make Shen Tianbai think
he has already won.
When someone gets close to success,
they're most likely to slip up.
I see.
If Shen Tianbai is faking his amnesia
and infiltrated the Qingtian Gang
with ulterior motives,
he'll definitely take advantage
of the opportunity tonight
and take a look at the ledger.
Then we'll expose him right to his face.
Uncle Zhong,
give me the key to the warehouse.
I will deliver the ledger myself.
Yes.
[Eclipse in the Lost City]
[Episode 4]
Young Master.
Don't move.
You are injured.
Just lie down.
Does it still hurt?
No.
Liar.
You've got so many injuries.
You're not made of iron.
How could it not hurt?
Actually...
I've remembered a few things.
What?
Some things
from school.
Young Master,
did we know each other a long time ago?
Who at school
didn't know you?
Then were we friends?
No.
We were never friends.
Lu Ye,
you won't even lie to me?
Uncle Zhong made this calming soup.
Here you go.
Drink it while it's warm.
Young Master.
You should go back and get some rest.
I can't rest.
I still have to put the ledger away.
Do you know
why I have to get this?
I'm not telling you.
Alright.
I'm off.
Shen Tianbai.
Sweet dreams.
You too.
Young Master.
The light is on.
Could it really be Shen Tianbai?
Let's go.
Shen Tianbai,
you—
The light...
I'll wait here all night.
I don't believe
I can't wait you out, you little thief.
[Lu Mansion]
Young Master.
Didn't you sleep well?
You slept pretty well.
Thanks to the calming soup
you brought me last night.
[The night before]
Something's wrong.
Are you looking for this one?
This looks like the second volume.
Excuse me, coming through.
Who is
disturbing my sleep?
You.
You...
So you are Lu Ye.
Scared?
My dad is Lu—
Your dad asked me
to keep an eye on you at school.
So come back to class with me.
Shen Tianbai?
You're the transfer student
my dad is always talking about.
Your dad sponsored me.
In return,
I'm responsible
for looking after your studies.
Come with me.
Mr. Shen.
I've long heard that you are
handsome, dashing,
and brilliantly gifted.
Seeing you today,
you truly live up to your reputation.
Because it's the truth.
So what?
Oh no.
I've finally met my match
when it comes to shamelessness.
So,
let's be friends.
You just got here.
There's nowhere in Ningcheng I don't know.
I'll show you around.
You want me to skip class with you?
That's impossible.
I genuinely want to be your friend.
This chocolate is hard to come by.
I wouldn't give it to just anyone.
Who is this guy?
He's so handsome.
No need.
I'm not interested.
Shen Tianbai, you will regret this.
Tianbai.
Bye.
A flat tire?
You almost
caught me.
Sweet dreams.
You too.
Lu Ye.
After all these years,
you really haven't changed at all.
Young Master.
The guests you invited are here.
Really?
Please show them in.
Yes.
I'll take you to meet them.
They're all old friends of mine.
Young Master.
Enough with
the childish tantrums.
Hand over the ledger.
Out of respect for the old chief,
[Qinglong, Qingtian Gang]
I'll let this one slide.
What?
Aren't we here today
to get the Qingtian Gang's token?
[Zhuque, Qingtian Gang]
What's the rush?
Qinglong, Zhuque.
Take a seat.
Serve the tea.
Shen Tianbai?
Why are you here?
Weren't you missing?
What?
Was killing the old chief not enough?
Are you not going
to spare his son, either?
Alright.
Come back.
Lu Ye.
You brat.
Are you crazy?
This is the man who killed your father!
Qinglong.
Who said you could speak
to Young Master like that?
The old chief is gone,
but I'm still alive.
We don't even know for sure
who killed my father.
What do you mean?
Baihu is dead.
Xuanwu is by my side.
Qinglong and Zhuque
have set up their own factions.
I really can't figure it out.
There's a mole in our Qingtian Gang,
and they even got my father killed.
You brat.
I don't have time to play games with you.
As for the ledger,
just you wait.
Let's go.
I've planted explosives all over the yard.
Take one step out that door,
and...
Boom!
Who are you trying to scare?
Qinglong, Zhuque.
Tell me.
Who was it?
Damn it.
Why don't you suspect him?
Xuanwu.
Stop pretending.
If you ask me,
it's you.
Is that so?
Young Master.
What exactly do you want to do?
Isn't it obvious?
Shut the door and catch the dog!
Yes.
I'll take you down first!
Shen Tianbai.
You spineless coward!
You can even forget the man
who killed your father?
I can't believe the old chief
had a coward like you for a son.
Young Chief?
Bah!
Qinglong.
Don't rush.
Officer Shen has too much pride
to take credit for something he didn't do.
If he's so sure he didn't kill him,
then I should at least give him
a chance to explain.
But
if he can't explain himself,
I will kill him myself.
Officer Shen,
any objections?
I have evidence left by the mole.
The police got word
that after Lu Wenbiao died,
someone picked up the Qingtian Gang's
most valuable shipment
from the north branch.
They even signed the warehouse logbook.
If we check them one by one,
we will find out whose men they are.
Young Master.
It wasn't me.
I swear on my life.
Then it must be you.
Qinglong.
I had the goods taken.
Did some brainless idiot sign for it?
Those idiots working for Biao really
would do something that stupid.
No.
What if they are bluffing me?
Bullshit.
Trying to frame me?
Where is the evidence?
Page 27, second row, fifth column.
Come on.
I'll give you one last chance
to come clean.
Once you open it,
there's no turning back.